提筆逐漸變困難
It's getting hard to write
時間也已這麼晚
and late into the night
有好一陣子了，我還在往地上扔信
It's been while now, I toss the mail around
希望你最近過得好
I hope you've been alright
我仍急迫想知道
I'm eager just to know
從此我該往何方
where, from this point, I go
我想你也知道，交朋友我都有做到
'Cause I can tell you now, I've made my way around
但我似乎未曾成長
but I never seem to grow
若你能看懂這封信件
If you can see right through this letter
想必眼淚也會流滿面
then all the tears are clearly shown
我想就這樣也許更好
I guess it must be for the better
但我希望能讓你知道
but I just thought I'd let you know
墨水已快被寫乾
My ink is running out
午夜也即將到來
as midnight comes around
想想也說夠了，我應該寫的都寫了
I guess I'll close it up, I think I've said enough
反正一直都是缺回信
'cause I'm just waiting for you now
若你能看懂這封信件
If you can see right through this letter
想必眼淚也會流滿面
then all the tears are clearly shown
我想就這樣也許更好
I guess it must be for the better
但我希望能讓你知道
but I just thought I'd let you know
若你能看懂這封信件
If you can see right through this letter
(能看懂我)
(See right through me)
想必眼淚也會流滿面
then all the tears are clearly shown
(淚流滿面)
(Tears are surely shown)
就算知道你不會回覆
And still, I know you'll never answer
(永不回覆)
(Never answer)
我仍希望能讓你知道
but I just thought I'd let you know
(希望能讓你...)
(Thought I'd let you...)